Guide to the Kermit Carlyle Parsons papers, circa 1945-1999
Parsons, Kermit Carlyle papers, circa 1945-1999
- Series III. Research and Consulting
  - Consulting
    - Korean Reports, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - World Bank Korea Project, 1980-1992 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - World Bank Korea Project, 1980-1992 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Korean Project - Photos, undated (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - CRP 776 outline and KTA correspondence, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Parsons' Report to World Bank on Central Wholesale Market, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Consultant's report for Mexico marketing project for World Bank, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Agency for International Development correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Parsons World Bank Job Application, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - International Development and Energy Associates; US AID, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Specifications for a Residence for Mr. & Mrs. Allyn C. Swinnerton, 1951 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - PDR Request for Proposals and subsequent research papers, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Preliminary floor plan of National Trust for Historic Preservation New Headquarter, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Federal Trade Commission request for proposal, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Conifer Development, Inc. vs. The City of Syracuse - correspondence and legal documents, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Manila, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Plan of Park Forest, 1956 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Proposed New Zoning Ordinance for the City of Ithaca, 1959 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - The Description of the Redevelopment Plan and Supporting Documentation, Longwood Development Project, ca. 1954 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - The Description of the Redevelopment Plan and Supporting Documentation, Longwood Development Project, ca. 1954 (Box 117, Folder 5)
- Series IV. Cornell University Faculty and Administrative Files
  - "The Cornell Idea", undated (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Introducing Cornell: Cornell University Announcements, undated (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Oral Examination Procedure, undated (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - AAP programs brochure, Undated (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Willard Straight Hall Report, undated (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - The Cornellian, 1932 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Cornell programs and booklets, 1952-1990 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Research Files, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Planning for Urban Aesthetics, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Events around Cornell and Ithaca, 1962-78 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - The Terms of the Truce between Universities and Cities, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Reports and newspapers about campus development, 1966-95 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - "Cornell University Report to the President", 1967-1968 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - A Program in Transportation for Cornell University, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Who's Who--K.C., 1968 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - University Unrest newspaper articles, 1968-1969 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - University Unrest journal articles, 1968-1969 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - University Unrest journal articles, 1968-1969 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - "Cornell University Annual Report", 1969-1970 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper clippings from The Cornell Daily Sun, 1970s (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - "Engineering Cornell Quarterly", Autumn 1971 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Cornell campus development reports, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - The building of the Henry Sage House, 1971-74 (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - CU Faculty Handbook, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Cornell newspapers, 1973-1984 (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Cornell University budget 1974-1975 fiscal year, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Cornell University Commencement, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Factual Profile of Cornell University, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - "Arnold Singer: Drawings and Prints" Program, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - "The Emens Lectures: Owings, Spreiregen, Bonta, 1974-1975 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Ithaca's Bikeway Study, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Alumni News, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - The Cornell Idea, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Memorandum, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Women at Cornell Brochure, 1977 (aprox) (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Statements - Cornell Press, 1977-1988 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - "Cornell's Changing Context" by Rhodes, May 1978 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Quarterly Financial Report, 9/30/1978 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Statements - Cornell University Faculty, 1978-1979 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Minority Education Council, 1978-1979 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition of Work by Students of AAP 1871-1977, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - CAAP annual report, August 1980 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - AAP Alumni Newsletter, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - "Jason Seley", 1980 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Cornell publications and book, 1980-1982 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - "John Hartell: Large Paintings since 1968", 1982 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Cornell News Articles, 1983-1999 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - "The 1986 State of the University Report", 1986 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Cornell reports, 1984-97 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Stuart Blumin Promotion files - criteria and procedures of reviews for promotion, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Stuart Blumin manuscript and research proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous publications, correspondence, 1985-99 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Communique, Summer 1987 (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and KCP's commencement program, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Cornell AAP anniversary book and misc correspondence, 1989-96 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Cornell brochures and publications, 1989-97 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Documentation Newsletter, Spring 1990 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Campus Second Edition Visuals and Articles, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Creating the Future: The Cornell Campaign for the College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Charles Zeller Klauder on the Campus of Cornell University, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - "Jack Squire: Sculpture Retrospective (1953-1993)", August 1993 (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - Assessment of Cornell Architecture Dept's collection on mounted photographs, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Dragon Day Photos, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 37)
  - Corson Dinner Invitation, 5/28/1994 (Box 87, Folder 38)
  - Ecological Industrial Park Proposal: Baltimore, Maryland (Work and Environment Initiative), 1994 (Box 87, Folder 39)
  - AAP Newsletter Fall 1995, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 40)
  - Bicycles on Campus Correspondence, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 41)
  - Department of CRP Alumni - 1950-1995, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 42)
  - "Architectural Program Report", 1997 (Box 87, Folder 43)
  - Institute for Urban and Landscape Studio, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 44)
  - Cornell Dept of Architecture Faculty Exhibit, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Brochures, 1998-? (Box 87, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous Brochures, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 47)
  - Cornell AAP brochures and alumni newsletters, 1995-2003 (Box 87, Folder 48)
  - Cornell University Brochure, undated (Box 87, Folder 49)
  - McGraw Tower Photograph, Undated (Box 87, Folder 50)
  - City and Regional Planning (CRP) Administration
    - CRP Course Offerings, 1950-1953 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Student Semester Hours, 1956-1965 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - City Planning Education Files, 1957-1958 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Eldridge, May 11, 1905 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - CRP- Sargent Webster Crenshaw & Folley Architects Program Files, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Burnham Kelly Introduction, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Clark, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - CRP Curriculum, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Organization of Cornell Planners Conference Notes, 1960s (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - CRP Department Financial Statements and Budgets, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Departmental Reports - Alumni Lists, 1961-1967 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Departmental Reports - Alumni Lists, 1961-1967 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Academic Conduct, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Departmental Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - Katz, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Laidlaw, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Visiting Lecturer Files, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - CRP Student Files, 1962-1965 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - CRP Student Files, 1962-1965 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - CRP Curriculum Notes and Schedules, 1962-1963 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Wallays, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - CRP Alumni Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - CRP Department Budget, Course, and Research Correspondence, 1962; 1971; 1975 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence, Reports - Institutional Planning, 1963; 1970; 1978 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Campus Lecture Committee, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Sibley Offices, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - City & Regional Planning Departmental Files, 1964-1967 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - City & Regional Planning Departmental Files, 1964-1967 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - City & Regional Planning Departmental Files, 1964-1967 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - CRP and Cornell University Financial Notes and Reports, April 1964 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Lecture on Campus Design - Planning Seminar, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Report on CRP Department, Fall 1964 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Cornell University - CRP Department News, January 20, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - Faculty Vitae - Jack Fisher, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - AIP - Upstate New York, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - CRP Department Alumni Lists and Correspondence, '1966 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - CRP Department Alumni Lists and Correspondence, '1966 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - CRP New York City Field Trips and Internships, 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - CRP New York City Field Trips and Internships, 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - CRP New York City Field Trips and Internships, 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - CRP New York City Field Trips and Internships, 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Faculty/Student Seminar, 1966/1967 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - CRP Department Correspondence and Notes, 1966-1969 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - CRP Department Correspondence and Notes, 1966-1969 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - CRP Department Courses, 1966-1969 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - CRP Department Courses, 1966-1969 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - CRP Curriculum Correspondence and Notes, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Sibley Floor Plan, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Departmental Space Study, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - West Sibley Construction - Adanlock, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Department Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Department Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Department Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - MRP Curriculum Study, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - MRP Curriculum Discussion, Spring 1968 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - 11th Organization of Cornell Planners, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - American Society of Planning Officials - Survey Reports, Planning Schools, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - CRP Faculty Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, Curriculum, 1968-1971 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Documents - First-Year MRP Exam Boycott, March 1968 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Vitae, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Department Meeting agenda, notes, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Department Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, November 1969 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Human Affairs Program, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - New York City - Summer Internship, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - CRP New York City Internship Program, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - University Planning Institute, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Department Notes and Correspondence, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Douglas A. Brown - Ad Hoc Committee, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Cornell Urban Development Program: Notes, faculty correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Cornell Urban Development Program: Notes, faculty correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, May-June 1970 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Department Correspondence, June 1970 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - CRP Course Outlines, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Department Correpsondence, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Cornellians in Planning, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Social Planning Faculty Position, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Urban Studies - Graduate Field, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Cornell Planning, Urban Development Research Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Department Reorganization, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous articles and correspondence, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Departmental Correspondence, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - University of Florida - Urban Planning Program Establishment, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Departmental Correspondence and Notes, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Departmental Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - CRP Adminstrative Correspondence, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - CRP 50th Anniversary Files, 1976-1980 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Cornell Program Announcements and Brochures, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Washington/Baltimore Program - Early Planning History, 1977-1980 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Washington/Baltimore Program - Early Planning History, 1977-1980 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Phone Lists, Meeting Minutes, 1977-1983 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - KC Parsons sabbatical files, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Notes, 1980-1984 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Meeting with Abrams and Vail- New York City, May 2, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and reports, 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Cornell Planning Newsletters, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Department Correspondence, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - CRP-Korea Materials, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Urban and Regional Studies Faculty Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Departmental Correspondence, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - History of Architecture and Urban Development, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Luis Suarez-Villa, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - CRP Faculty Resumes, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Recommendations - Moss, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - CRP Department Notes and Reports, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Grad Student Correspondence, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Recommendations - Carvalho, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - History Preservation - Burnham Kelly, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - CRP Alumni Files, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - CRP Department Correspondence, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - CRP Evaluation Notes, Minutes, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Cornell in Washington - Summer Files, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - David Lewis Memo Regarding CRP Handbook, April 2, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Cornell in Washington - Faculty Correspondence, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Department Faculty/Staff Contact List, Spring 1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Outline and History of City and Regional Planning Department, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - CRP - Washinton Program, Teaching Compensation Notes, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Cornell in Washington - Linda Johnson Housing, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Speaker Correspondence, Fall 1987 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Cornell in Washington, '1987 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Cornell in Washington Files, '1988 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Cornell in Washington - Students, '1988 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Cornell in Washington - Teaching, '1988 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - CRP Departmental Correspondence, '1988 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - CRP Faculty Files, 1989-1990 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - KC Parsons Department Correspondence, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Departmental Correspondence with some Class notes, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Department Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Department Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Department Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Stein Fellowship Information, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Real Estate Program Files, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - CRP Course Descriptions, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Sabbatical Files, 1994; 1996 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Departmental Correspondence, Agendas, March 1995 - 1996 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Stein Institute Files, 1995-1997 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Stein Fellowship Files, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Department Correspondence, Notes, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Teresa Cameron Recommendations, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and reports, 1996-1998 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - Bill Fulton Correspondence, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - Barclay Jones Obituary, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - Sibley Hall Renovation, 1998-1999 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Department Files, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - Faculty Files, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Department Files, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 37)
    - MRP Admission Statistics and Reports, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Collection of Regional History and the University Archives, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Barnes Hall Protest Files, 1962-1965 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - News of the CRP department, 1965-1968 (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - MRP Program Description and Correspondence, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Sibley Lounge - Past, Present and Future, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Cornell University Finance Study, September 1970 (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Cornell-Community Relations Study, August 1970 (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - MRP Admission Statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Parsons Travel Reimbursements, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - A Proposal to Establish a Master's Level Program in Social Policy Planning, January 1972 (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - The Cornell University Master Plan 1971-72 through 1980-81 (Draft), February 1972 (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Training Program, February 1972 (Box 93, Folder 35)
    - Cornell University Annual Report, 1975-1975 (Box 93, Folder 36)
    - Program in Historic Preservation Planning, 1981-1985 (Box 93, Folder 37)
    - M. Arch Program report, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 38)
  - Art, Architecture and Planning (AAP) Administration
    - Feldt, Alan G., 1959 - 1971 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Correspondence, grants, proposals, curriculum vitae, SOC 435 class outline and reading list
    - Jones, Barclay G., 1961 - 1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Correspondence, policy statement, papers, reports, grants
    - Stein, Stuart W., 1966 - 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      Resume, memos, correspondence, proposals
    - Comprehensive Health Planning, Barclay G. Jones, 1960 - 1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Correspondence, memos, grants, City Planning 100 syllabus, proposals, reports
    - College of Architecture Council correspondence, 1961 - 1962 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Landscape Architecture Council correspondence, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - The Book of the College of Architecture, Cornell University, 1903 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Early History of the College of Architecture, 1923-1948 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Early History of the College of Architecture, 1923-1948 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Course Schedules; 1957-59, 1957-1959 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - College of Architecture Committee, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Alumni Newsletters, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Cornell University College of Architecture Alumni Directory, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Historical College of Architecture Articles and Notes, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - College of Architecture Retrospective, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Cornell College of Architecture - New York City Program, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Cornell College of Architecture - New York City Program, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - "The Teaching of Design in New Architectural Curriculums", 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - "Teaching of Design in New Architectural Curriculums" Extra Copy, 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Course Schedules; 1963, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Trustee Files, 1964-1968 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Trustee Files, 1964-1968 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Trustee Files, 1964-1968 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Newsletters, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - College Educational Policy Committee, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - College Curriculum Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - New York City Travel Files, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Alumni Newsletters, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Hartel Committee, 1966;1971 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Degrees Conferred, 1966,1971 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Course Schedules; 1965-1966, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Course Schedules; 1966-1967, 1966-1967 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Jack Fisher Files, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - New York City Program Brochure, October 1967 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Course Schedules; 1967, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Recommendations & Awards, 1967-1984 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - College of Architecture Curriculum Committee, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Graduate Research and Scholarship in Architectural Education, prepared by the Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture Files, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture Files, '1968 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Course Schedules; 1968, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - AAP Correspondence, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Letters to/from Georgia Davis, 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Architecture Study - Report to Provost, October 1970 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Architecture Study Committee - Meeting Minutes, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Department of Architecture Curriculum Committee, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Department of Architecture Subcommittee Background Materials, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Department of Architecture Operations Study, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Architecture Study Committee Report to the Provost, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Budget Files - Graduate Faculty Statistics, 1970-1974 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - "Architecture Study Committee - Report to the Provost", October 20, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Architecture Study Committee, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - AAP Curriculum files, correspondence, notes, 1971-1973 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - AAP Annual Report, 1971-1973 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Simone Clemhout's Papers, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Annual Reports: College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1971/72-1979/80 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Annual Reports: College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1971/72-1979/80 (Box 64, Folder 20)